infocrystals.com 2011-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Infocrystals.com | Infocrystals - Article repository

## Privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Updated: 05.05.2011**

I respect you as my visitor and I guarantee that I commit in protecting your privacy when you are online in my [www.infocrystals.com](http://www.infocrystals.com/). The below following are our content distribution practices for our website infocrystals.com

Log Files

Most of the standard servers use log files, We at infocrystals.com use log files. This Includes ip address, browser type, ISP provider, your viewing resolution, Referring /exit page, operating system, date and time, and calculate the clicks to analyze visitor trends, ability to administer our website effective, track user’s movement in the aggregate and collect broad information about the demographic location and IP addresses. I guarantee is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Subscription**  
We have a facility for subscribing to our posts. You can subscribe through Feed burner. When user subscribes for the email , I used to ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to this information. My site will display ads related to  Google That is our only Revenue source. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Update for Google Adsense and DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables them to serve ads to you based on your visit to this blog as well as other sites on the Internet.

As users, you may opt out of the use of this DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) page.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy you can [contact](mailto:info@infocrystals.com) me.
